Well, with the 215th overall pick, the
Atlanta Falcons selected Harold Perkins
Jr., the linebacker out of LSU. First of
all, Harold, congratulations. Welcome to
Atlanta. This has been such a long time
coming for you to be drafted to the NFL.
What does this moment mean to you right
now?
>> She didn't mean anything. I've been
waiting on this moment for 23 years.
>> Kind of walk me through getting the
phone call. What did it feel like to see
404 pop up on your screen? And what who
was on the other side of the call when
you answered?
Can't remember which coach it was, but I
know they was all excited to talk to me,
but the moment it was just so real. At
first, I I was just cooling, chilling
with my family, just, you know, waiting
my turn for real. Then my phone started
ringing. I looked, the first name I saw
was Atlanta Falcons. First thing I said,
let's do it.
>> Love it. You are joining a defense that
is headed up by defensive coordinator
Jeff Olrich. He was a linebacker
himself. He loves linebackers, inside
linebackers, outside linebackers, loves
them all. How excited are you to join
this defense under Jeff Brick?
>> Man, I'm excited. I'm ready to be a
bird.
>> For the guy, for the fans that might not
know a ton about your playing style, can
you quickly explain what you're bringing
to the field for the Atlanta Falcons?
>> Bringing explosiveness, bringing that
dog, that savage, and the aggressive
mindset ready to do it.
>> Love it. I see you got a hat on. Can I
see kind of what you're wearing right
now? What you got on the hat? There we
go. There he is, ladies and gentlemen,
the newest Atlanta Falcon, Harold
Perkins Jr., thank you so much.
Congratulations on being a Falcon and
welcome to Atlanta.
>> I appreciate y'all for having me.